<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Clean and Comfort</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="dismiss">dismiss</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Register</string>
    <string name="minimum_password">Password too short, enter minimum 6 characters!</string>
    <string name="auth_failed">Authentication failed, check your email and password or sign up</string>
    <string name="change_email">Change Email</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="send_password_reset_email">Send Password reset email</string>
    <string name="remove_user">Remove user</string>
    <string name="new_pass">New Password</string>
    <string name="title_activity_profile">Firebase</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_mobile">Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="hint_name">User Name</string>
    <string name="btn_login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_register">Not a member? Get registered here.</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_login">Already registered. Login Me!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_reset_password">ResetPasswordActivity</string>
    <string name="btn_forgot_password">Forgot your password?</string>
    <string name="btn_reset_password">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="btn_back"><![CDATA[<< Back]]></string>
    <string name="hint_new_email">New Email</string>
    <string name="btn_change">Change</string>
    <string name="btn_send">Send</string>
    <string name="btn_remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="btn_sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="lbl_forgot_password">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="forgot_password_msg">We just need your registered Mobile number and Username to reset your password.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Section 1</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Section 2</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Section 3</string>

    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>


    <string name="action_add_favourite">Add to Favourites</string>
    <string name="action_play_next">Play Next</string>
    <string name="backdrop_title">LOVE MUSIC</string>
    <string name="backdrop_subtitle">This season top 20 albums</string>

    <string name="Company_Profile">COMPANY PROFILE :
Samar Floor is one of the premier brands in imported wooden floorings and accessories. Based in Pune and with more than 15 years of experience, Samar Floor has come a long way in establishing itself as a reputed solution provider for wooden floors. It has earned the trust of countless customers and dealers alike. Associated with leading brands that are recognized and respected by the best in Indian Interior designing professionals, Samar Floor is a trusted name in the industry whose clientele includes leading corporate groups, hotels, builders and retailers. Having acquired expertise over the years we have diversified to fulfill the increasing demand for specialized floors. With an extensive range of laminated wooden floor, engineered flooring, solid wood flooring, deck and sports flooring, rubber tiles, vinyl sheets, carpet tiles, artificial grass, waterproof floors the company offers the most comprehensive alternate flooring solutions.</string>

    <string name="job_profile">JOB PROFILE :
Specialists in installations of wood floors and claddings, we at Samar Floor have been working throughout western India for over 15 years. We are involved in every aspect of the process, from meeting with the client to the final finishing details. Our company assures the highest level of workmanship and customer service.We offer a wide variety of wooden floors, to suit anything from small apartments, outdoor terraces to sprung floors in gymnasiums. We can create a new floor, overlay an old floor, or repair or extend an existing floor. Along with polyurethane finishes, we also offer oils, waxes and color stains to add an element of difference. Experienced in both commercial and residential settings, we work with architects and designers as well as individual clients. We supply a wide range of solid timber flooring (both tongue and groove, and parquet). These can be finished by applying stains from pale whitewashes to dark chocolate brown/black and everything in between.

We also supply an extensive range of quality prefinished engineered flooring, covering a wide selection of timber colors and finishes. The allure of laminate flooring lies not only in its representation of real hardwood and its incredible durability, but also in the ease with which these floors are installed and maintained. Our laminate flooring is available in a plethora of styles and designs.Our Wooden Floors are committed to being eco-friendly. We take great pride in the quality of both our materials and workmanship.After discussing your options and requirements with you, our comprehensive quotes leave nothing to surprise and we aim to work in with your building budget. Each installation comes with our warrantee and our after sales service means we are able to remedy any problems that occur.We at SAMAR AGENCIES enjoy the challenge of the new and interesting projects we undertake. The large varieties of projects we have worked on over the years are testament to our high standards and quality of workmanship.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cropimage">Cropimage</string>

    <string name="reg_member">Member Registration</string>
    <string name="mem_details">Member Details</string>
    <string name="mem_ward">WARD NUMBER</string>
    <string name="mem_name">NAME</string>
    <string name="mem_age">AGE</string>
    <string name="mem_dob">D.O.B.</string>
    <string name="mem_education">EDUCATION</string>
    <string name="mem_occupation">OCCUPATION</string>
    <string name="mem_tempaddress">TEMPORARY ADDRESS</string>
    <string name="mem_peraddress">PERMANENT ADDRESS</string>
    <string name="mem_curaddress">CURRENT ADDRESS</string>
    <string name="mem_contact">CONTACT NUMBER</string>
    <string name="mem_cast">CAST</string>
    <string name="mem_gender">GENDER</string>
    <string name="mem_male">Male</string>
    <string name="mem_female">Female</string>
    <string name="mem_voteridnumber">VOTER ID NUMBER</string>
    <string name="mem_relative">RELATION</string>
    <string name="mem_submit">SUBMIT</string>

    <string name="rel_name">MAIN PERSON NAME</string>
    <string name="rel_contact">CONTACT NUMBER</string>
    <string name="rel_address">ADDRESS</string>
    <string name="rel_details">Relation Details</string>
    <string name="rel_form">RELATION FORM</string>

    <string name="report_heading">Select from Date and to Date</string>
    <string name="report_fromdate">From Date</string>
    <string name="report_todate">To Date</string>
    <string name="report_PDF">PDF</string>

    <string name="generate_pdf_english">Generate PDF</string>

    <string name="mem_report_details_english">MEMBER REPORT DETAILS</string>

    <string name="mem_update">UPDATE</string>

    <string name="loading">Loading</string>
    <string name="PLEASE_WAIT">Please Wait</string>
    <string name="please_wait">Please wait</string>
    <string name="MOBILE_NUMBER_SHOULD_NOT_BE_EMPTY">Mobile number should not be empty.</string>
    <string name="MOBILE_NUMBER_ALREADY_REGISTER">Mobile number already register.</string>
    <string name="INVALID_MOBILE_NUMBER">Invalid mobile number.</string>
    <string name="PASSWORD_SHOULD_NOT_BE_EMPTY">Password should not be empty.</string>
    <string name="SIGNING_IN">Signing in</string>
    <string name="login_fail_try_again">Login fail, please try again with correct login details.</string>
    <string name="server_error">Faild to fetch data, please try again.</string>

    <string name="file_uploading_progress">Uploading in progress</string>
    <string name="file_uploading_complited">Uploading to server done </string>
    <string name="file_uploading_complited_message">Total uploaded files :&#160; </string>
    <string name="notification_message">Don\'t close the app.</string>




    <string name="application">By using our services, you agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions which may change from time to time without notice
</string>

    <string name="PAYMENT_TERMS">All quoted prices are subject to change without notice. All invoices must be paid on collection of garments or as otherwise directed by us and we reserve the right to retain your goods until your payment in full is received.</string>

    <string name="PICKUP_DELIVERY">Pickup- and delivery will be at our top priority. We will try to honor the times that you have specified for the pickup and delivery. However, due to certain restrictions and delays, we shall not be liable for delays. Kindly check the filled slip before handing over the clothes to the rider. Unless itemized list is sent with the laundry, our count must be accepted. In event that garments are not collected within thirty (30) days, we reserve the right to dispose them as we see fit and shall not be liable for any loss that you may suffer in such an event.

We examine each garments after we receive them at our warehouse and notify if any damage is observed. However, we don\'t guarantee that every damage will be identified before processing.</string>

    <string name="SAFE_CLEANING">We offer a safe cleaning guarantee. This means we will process every garments we accept safely. This does not mean we will remove every stain from every garment. If it is our professional opinion that stain removal will be unsafe, or will compromise our safe cleaning guarantee, stain removal efforts will cease.</string>

    <string name="DAMAGE">We exercise utmost care in cleaning and processing garments entrusted to us and use such process which, in out opinion, are best suited to the nurture and conditions of each individual garment, Nevertheless, we cannot assume the responsibility for inherent weaknesses or defects in materials (such as sun fading) which may result in tears or the development of small holes in fabric that are not readily apparent prior to processing. In dry-cleaning and laundering we cannot guarantee against color loss, color bleeding, embroidery color beads, buttons, pasting damage or any kind of wear and tear and shrinkage; or against damage to weak and tender fabrics.

Our liability with respect to any damage caused by us shall not exceed ten (10) times our charge for cleaning that garment regardless of brand or condition with an upper limit of Rs 2000. The compensation can only be redeemed as free service from Pick My Laundry.</string>

    <string name="LOSS_GARMENTS">We take utmost care in processing garments received to avoid misplacement or loss of items. We count and tag with unique bar code to each garments once we receive them at our warehouse. The clothes after processing are counted and scanned before packaging. However, there may be instance when items get misplaced or lost. Our liability with respect to any loss item shall not exceed ten (10) times our charge for cleaning that garment regardless of brand or condition with an upper limit of Rs 2000. The compensation can only be redeemed as free service from Pick My Laundry.</string>

    <string name="PERSONEL_ITEMS">Please check all your garments for money, jewelry or other valuables prior to handing over them to us. If we find any valuables in your garments, we will make every effort to return them to you but we cannot be held liable for the loss of any such articles that are forwarded to us.</string>

    <string name="COUNTING_GARMENTS">Please count all the garments during pickup and get it mentioned on this slip. We recount the clothes at our warehouse as we receive it. If there is any mismatch, it will be notified to you. However, we won’t be liable if we do not receive any response from you. During delivery, it is advisable to count all the clothes in front of rider and report any anomaly. No complaint will be entertained if it is reported after rider has left.</string>

    <string name="PRICING">The prices of laundry and dry-cleaning items are mentioned on our website and app. We reserve the right to change them without any prior notice to you. Furthermore, there are few specific garments such as lehenga, saree, kurta, etc. whose prices quoted are notional. The actual price can only be determined when our experts examine them at our warehouse.</string>

    <string name="PRIVACY">We will use your information in regular course of providing services to you. We respect your privacy and warrant that any information you give us will be held with the utmost care and security, and will be used in way to which you have not consented.</string>


</resources>
